cad-comic.com 2017-03-23

# Ctrl+Alt+Del - Privacy Policy

Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions, producer of Ctrl+Alt+Del and its related content and service sites, believes that electronic privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, commercial, and entertainment medium. We know you're concerned about protecting your privacy online.

At Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions, we treat your personal information with the highest standards of safety, security, and confidentiality.

 **Information Gathered**

We don't collect personal information without your knowledge. We don't sell, rent, or give your personal information to unrelated third parties without your prior permission.

This policy explains what information we collect about you and how we use that information. We also outline the choices you have. 

 **Cookies**

The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions cannot and does not control these cookies. 

 **Traffic Data**

Each time a visitor comes to a Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions site, information is collected to improve the overall quality of Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions sites. Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions collects the visitor's domain name/IP Address (e.g., whether the user is logged on from netscape.com or yale.edu or 255.255.255.0), referral data (e.g., we record the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to an Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions site), and browser/platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform).

In addition to collecting these types of information, Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions's advertisement delivery system collects aggregate search terms for internal reporting and targeted advertising. Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions's advertisement delivery system collects visitor information for purposes of product monitoring, product improvement, and targeted advertising.

Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions also counts, tracks, and aggregates the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flow at Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions sites (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from and how traffic flows within the sites). Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions may merge this information into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with potential advertisers, research firms, and business partners. Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions will not disclose your individual identity or personal data. When Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions does present aggregated information to potential advertisers, research firms, and business partners, no one will be able to identify you or contact you. 

 **E-mail Services**

Any/all e-mail addresses sent to us as the result of correspondence with the consumers of Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions will not be used or collected for the purposes of reselling to a third party and will not be added to a bulk e-mailing list.

Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions provides users the opportunity to opt-in and opt-out of receiving e-mail communications from us. This is made available during sign-up for our e-mail lists and in e-mail messages delivered from Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions. For any list managed by Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions, users can use the link in the footer of most e-mail messages to unsubscribe. 

 **Sharing and Usage Of Information**

Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions never shares, sells, or rents any personal information without your permission, unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information. 

 **Copyright**

Ctrl+Alt+Del® is a web comic published by Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions.

Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions® uses invented names in all its stories, except in cases when public figures are being satirized. Any other use of real names is accidental and coincidental.

The content of this web-site-graphics, text and other elements-is © Copyright 2002 by Tim Buckley and Ctrl+Alt+Del Productions, and may not be reprinted or retransmitted in whole or in part without the expressed written consent of the publisher.
